pacificpestinc.com 2012-09-21

# - Pacific Pest Control

## Rats Are Our Enemy

We are known to resolve numerous infestations such as Rats, Mice, Rodents, Ants, Spiders, Silverfish and more. Our services are affordable, effective, friendly and reliable. We offer a variety of solutions to seal all rodent entry points, sanitize and install TAP Insulation. We will make a barrier around your home for all pests.

Servicing Orange County, Los Angeles County, and San Diego County. Call for a free inspection.

#### News & Events

Diseases directly transmitted by rodents On this Page Hantavirus Pulmonary Syndrome Hemorrhagic Fever with Renal [...]

  Drywood and subterranean termites (coming up from the ground) are the most destructive insect [...]

Rodents destroy insulation, electrical wiring, plumbing, and other structural components of buildings. Insulation damage alone [...]

#### Client Testimonials

"Your technician just left, and it looks like he did a fine job spraying both inside and out. Thanks for stopping by. We look forward to seeing you again next time, and to a long and pest-free relationship."  
David - Palm Springs, CA

“We looked up Pacific Pest Control online and had them come to our home for a free quote. I was very pleased how professional and safety conscious our technician was. I even called them back out a week later since we still had some ants and they came over the next day.”   
Syed – Irvine, CA

"I have to say that these guys are my favorite. Friendly, easy to work with, honest, and effective. I would recommend them to everyone in the area."   
Tara – Indio, CA

### Privacy Policy

At [www.pacificpestinc.com](http://www.pacificpestinc.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us (See [this article](http://www.wp-insert.smartlogix.co.in/what-is-a-privacy-policy/) to learn more about Privacy Policies.). This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [www.pacificpestinc.com](http://www.pacificpestinc.com/) and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, [www.pacificpestinc.com](http://www.pacificpestinc.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
[www.pacificpestinc.com](http://www.pacificpestinc.com/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [www.pacificpestinc.com](http://www.pacificpestinc.com/).
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [www.pacificpestinc.com](http://www.pacificpestinc.com/) and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [www.pacificpestinc.com](http://www.pacificpestinc.com/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[www.pacificpestinc.com](http://www.pacificpestinc.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [www.pacificpestinc.com's](http://www.pacificpestinc.com/) privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
